coroflot.com 2019-03-30

# Coroflot — Design Jobs & Portfolios

  * ##  This website has agreed to notify you of: 

    * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the website.
    * The organization collecting the information.
    * How the information is used.
    * With whom the information may be shared.
    * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
    * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Coroflot's control.
    * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

  * ##  Information Collection and Use 

Coroflot is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Coroflot collects information from our users in several places on our site. 

  * ##  Registration 

In order to interact with this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to provide the user with the ability to log into the site to make additions or deletions. 

  * ##  Order 

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and billing address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

  * ##  Log Files 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

  * ##  Sharing 

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

  * ##  Links 

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Coroflot is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

  * ##  Newsletter 

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

  * ##  Security 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [support@coroflot.com](mailto:support@coroflot.com). 

  * ##  Supplementation of Information 

In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. 

For example, to determine if our customers qualify for one of our credit cards, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user's credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed. 

(or) 

In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partners, Company Y & Company Z, to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from either of these two companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences. 

  * ##  Correction/Updating Personal Information: 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@coroflot.com. 

  * ##  Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
